<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: personal | My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://BigGillyStyle.github.io/blog/categories/personal/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://BigGillyStyle.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-10-12T08:32:47-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://BigGillyStyle.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Andy Pickler]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trying out Octopress]]></title>
    <link href="http://BigGillyStyle.github.io/blog/2013/10/12/trying-out-octopress/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-12T08:13:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://BigGillyStyle.github.io/blog/2013/10/12/trying-out-octopress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my <strong>second</strong> attempt at getting a blog going.  My first, more ambitious attempt, was a full-blown Rails app with MongoDB as a back-end and a SASS Bootstrap themed front-end.  Sigh&hellip;and at about that same time I got my first Rails job, which is causing me to have to work 11-12 hour days with about 1-2 hours of &ldquo;awake time&rdquo; at home each evening (which is mostly spent eating, talking with my wife about our day, and then prepping for work and exercise the next day).  Long story a little less long&hellip;now I&rsquo;m trying out just using <a href="http://octopress.org">Octopress</a>, which greatly simplifies getting some content out there.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m learning plenty about full stack Rails and JavaScript development at work, so I don&rsquo;t need my blogging platform to be my &ldquo;gateway&rdquo; to my learning experience any more.  In fact, if all goes as planned (which it rarely does in life), then I can move on to implementing one of my &ldquo;great business ideas&rdquo;&hellip;and then using this simplified blogging platform to document my bumps and bruises along the way.  I promise no particular focus of this blog right now, as some days it may be technical in nature, and some days it may be these rambling personal thoughts.  It&rsquo;s a start.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
